thank you uh raymond and uh good evening
everyone
and thank you for joining us on this
call
you know these are unusual times and i
hope that you and your family
and all your close ones are safe let me
start by
introducing my colleagues who are with
me on this call i have gopal
balachandran our cfo
we have sanjeev mantri our executive
director retail
allo kagarwal our executive director
wholesale and loknaskar
our chief legal and compliance officer
so today is indeed a landmark day for us
as you would have probably seen we've
entered into definitive agreements with
bharti access general insurance
to acquire the non-life business of
bharti extra gi
this transaction is proposed to be
implemented via scheme of arrangement
under which bharti access gi's non-life
insurance business would be demerged
into icc number
this call is to discuss this notable
development which we think will
significantly shape the future prospects
of say salomon
at ices but as you have been seeing us
through the years
we've always worked with creating
long-term shareholder value
whether in terms of growth distribution
network or profitability
as part of our constant endeavor to look
for future growth drivers we've always
been open to looking at
inorganic opportunities this particular
case stood out for us for a few reasons
one this was an interesting opportunity
for us to acquire the non-life
business insurance business of a company
that is well reputed with strong
corporate governance and good management
team with a strong cultural fit
the company has in the last few years
been able to create a credible
distribution engine with
key partnerships and good traction that
is being built over the last few years
this distribution engine would
meaningfully enhance the number of
customer touch points for us
the company also has a serviceable
investment portfolio of
roughly about 47.65 billion rupees as at
uh
march uh 2020. uh this deal also
presented a strong proposition to
partner with the bharti group one of
india's
leading business groups and axa a well
regarded well-reputed large
global insurer and finally we've used
our stock as currency in this deal
and therefore did not require any
capital gains for funding this
transaction or for solvency going ahead
we are very excited about this
transaction and what this means for isis
lombard due to the compelling user
strategies both
in terms of revenue and costs that this
transaction brings to bear
when we look at the combined entity on a
pro forma basis we would be
at a market share of around 8.7 among
all non-life insurers in
india the transaction would enable us to
further consider
our leading position among among private
non-life insurers and we would
also become one of the top three
non-life insurers in the country
we've traditionally been very strong on
motor insurance and are currently the
number two player in the industry
with this transaction we would be able
to consolidate our market leading
position and increase our penetration
across oems
our combined market share and motor
insurance on a pro forma basis
for the year ended 31st march 2020 would
increase from 10 percent currently to 12
percent
on the bank account side bharti axa gi
has recently entered into meaningful
partnerships with large retail banking
platforms post this transaction we
expect that isis lumber would have
tie-ups with most of the leading private
banks in india
the addition of this large vacation
staffs provide provides a strong runway
for future growth
we hope to leverage our experience and
learnings from
successfully partnering with icc bank
and our deep penetration across the
country to deliver rapid success from
and deliver value to these bank
assurance partnerships
adding further on the distribution side
we would be able to add
roughly about thousand seven hundred
agents into our fold through this
transaction
but yes uh gi's agency force has grown
rapidly in the last
in the recent few years increasing from
uh four thousand agents in
2017 to the current level of 6700
regions
we have internally sharpened our own
focus on agency channel and we expect to
be in a position to internally
uh you know enhance our productivity
levels
of the agents as well another aspect
that has worked well for us in terms of
distribution is a relatively deeper
geographical penetration that we have
beyond the top
25 cities we have large presence even in
the tier 2 and tier 3 cities and this
footprint has really helped us in
driving business through the
distribution types that we have in those
countries in these cities
we hope to leverage our learnings and
replicate the success that we have had
with the new partnerships that we would
form as a result of these proposed
of this proposed transaction in terms of
cost
you would have seen that bhartiya gi
currently operates
at higher opex ratios as compared to us
as we combine our businesses going
forward we expect to benefit from
operating leverage
and cost effectiveness over time we
would be able to reduce
certain overheads such as branch
infrastructure cost information
technology cost branding and publicity
related costs etc as examples
given that we will be functioning as a
combined entity rather than two separate
ones
along with the compelling business
rationale that i spoke about this
transaction was also interesting from uh
for us
from a strategic point point standpoint
uh due to the opportunity to partner
with bhakti and axa groups
we are excited to be entering into this
partnership with bharti group which is
a large business house with diversified
interests we look forward to working
closely with them to provide customized
insurance solutions to their group
companies and customers
we are also enthused by the pros
prospects of working with axa
a large well-regulated local insurer and
to leverage their unique capabilities on
products risk management and reinsurance
solutions
before i conclude i would like to
elaborate on the transaction structure
bharti and axa groups would be issued
fresh shares of ics lombard as
consideration for this transaction post
completion of the transaction they would
own
approximately seven point three percent
stake in icc lombard on a combined
basis it is also important to highlight
the combined entity would be solvent
would have solvency margin well above
regulatory requirements thus eliminating
need for
any fund raise for the transaction
this transaction is of course subject to
various regulatory approvals we are
hopeful subject to the due approval
process that we should
we shall be able to complete this
proposed transaction speedily
so that we can commence business as one
single entity in the market immediately
thereafter
before i hand uh over the call to the
moderator i would like to thank the
party as our general insurance team and
welcome them to the icc lombard
franchise
i would also like to thank our
shareholders who've always
been very supportive and constantly
motivated us to keep forging ahead
and lastly my colleagues at isis lombard
will work diligently to make this
transaction happen
on that note i would like to hand it
over to the moderator and open the floor
for any questions that you may have
thank you thank you very much
we will now begin the question and
answer session anyone who wishes to ask
questions may press
star and one on the touchstone telephone
if you wish to remove yourself from the
question queue you may press star and
two
participants are requested to use
handsets while asking questions
ladies and gentlemen we will wait for a
moment while the question key assembles
to ask a question please press star and
one
the first question is from the line of
suresh kanti
from macquarie please go ahead
yeah hi uh btc can you share what is the
path
net worth and combine operating ratio
bharti axa as of f520
gopal you want to answer the name give
the numbers
yeah so they have they had made a loss
uh suresh
uh so that profit after tax for fi 20
then
they had a loss of 244 crores the
combined ratio which they had was about
120.4 percent
and as of march 2020 they had a net
worth of about 660
crores okay so you know uh
i have two questions here bdg for you
first it looks like the
price that your fade looks very high for
an entity which is making
a negative return point number one so
how do you justify such a high price for
this entity
secondly i am still not com comfortable
or confident about
what kind of synergies that you are
talking about because
you know either there has to be some
product complementarities or
geographical complementarities
or maybe some kind of opex synergy i
mean i'm hard-pressed to think
how do you justify this being in the
sense that this
did this deal come to you or you went
out for scouting
any such color would be greatly
appreciated yeah
yeah so no thanks uh sorry so uh in
terms of the deal this was a
you know curated bilateral deal we were
interested
uh and i guess as much as the
counterparty being also interested in
the transaction
um so there was no bidding process it
was just us
talking to them uh in terms of the way
we've looked at it we've uh
looked at multiple aspects of how we
ascribe value to this transaction
uh the way the valuers have looked at it
is basically
the market benchmark and as gopal
explained since there's no profits last
year of course there was a one-time
write-off on the investment book
last year but even apart from that if
you have a
you know loss there's no p e ratio to
compare but if you
compare the price to books for us
versus this entity and also look at
uh benchmark transactions that have that
have happened even without control
premium
you know the price to book for this
transaction comes to about roughly about
6.5 times book
which is similar to what uh where you've
seen deals in the market
and at 6.5 times book it's roughly about
almost 30
discount to our price to book multiple
at this point in time
you're the best insurance company in
india and far more profitable so
how can that be a benchmark yeah so
there is
the the benchmarks not just from our you
know
our discount perspective i was
explaining that even in the market those
are the standard benchmarks including
for
pure play health companies where the roe
model cannot be as
strong and you know let me continue with
the point that i was making so
in terms of the benefit that we see uh
there are both revenue and
cost synergies that we see as gopal
explained if you see the last year
number
their loss ratio was about 78 their
expense ratios are 42 one thing that you
realize in this industry is there are
significant scale benefits that we
benefit from for example uh if you look
at the loss ratio the loss ratio is not
way off the
charts you know from you know the the
most good players in the market
but the challenge that they're facing is
in the operating expense
ahead now obviously as a combined ratio
a combined entity we believe we'll
see significant synergies on the cost
side
on the revenue side we believe if you
see some of the recent
partnerships that we have signed up uh
with some
leading banks in in the country as also
the investment that they've made
in uh the agency channel so that
investment has been going on for the
last couple of years
and we believe the runway for growth on
this platform is
is long for us so we believe there'll be
incremental revenue
opportunities that we see and as i said
in the opening remarks you know
for them they've largely been the large
city
uh you know company their depth into the
smaller markets is not as
uh as much as us so with a national uh
tie-up we believe we'll be able to get
significantly more you know higher
benefits
in terms of this energy in the on the
revenue side so
you know both in terms of the benchmarks
that
we see in the market for deals in terms
of the synergy benefits both on revenue
side as also the cost side
and even our internal you know models
that we've used to value this company
very conservatively
believe we've paid a we've got a good
deal
thanks very this is one last question if
i might squeeze in
any uh any due diligence done which
which
which could have been which which would
eventually result in
any further write-offs now because you
said they took a write-off on their
investment portfolio
as all that been accounted for or do you
think as a part of the merger process
there could be some right of there and
there which you'll have to take
we've done the due diligence and they
have some you know some of the
investment assets for which they took a
write of last year
uh some residual amount left which is
factor in our valuation
okay fine thank you so much
thank you the next question is from the
line of
nadeshine from investing capital please
go ahead
from investor capital we can't hear you
hello is it audible yes
yeah so the first question is on overlap
in terms of distribution and geography
uh as i see rcx also has very strong oem
channel
and you also have a very strong oem
channel so
what what is that what is the overlap
and where you see
there will be a cannibalization of
revenue between the two entities
so in terms of oem you're right i mean
if you see they're much stronger motor
player
you know relatively among players and
they're pretty strong in the oem
channels
now having however if you look at within
each oem there are two
two aspects to look at one is at the oem
level and then at a dealer level
um and when you look at oem level there
are
three or four oem uh you know vms where
they're
pretty strong i mean in terms of their
relative position
they've got a very large share in some
of these uh platforms
uh in one of them they're kind of uh you
know
way ahead of us as well so so i think
there is some
synergy benefit that we will see there
could be some overlaps here and there
and there is a possibility
which we've already baked in our in our
numbers of some dc energies here and
there
but we are reasonably confident given
our uh ground level understanding of
what they do where they are
you know which direction they present in
we believe that
this will be uh you know the dc energy
effect will not be very large
sure sure and apart from motor other
segments
uh is there any strength that they bring
to table i don't see in
terms of for their their performance i
don't see any
significant strength in any other in any
other segment no i think that you know
for for them
last three years has been kind of an
investment in building up scale in
certain other
uh areas and one of the areas that
they've been focusing on
over the last three four years has been
the bankishan channel
and there i think what we've seen is one
they've entered into relationships
over the last couple of years only and
we probably haven't seen them fully ramp
up these
partnerships number one and even in bank
assurance
we see a lot of opportunity and what we
experience in terms of type of products
that we sell both on the sme and the
health
side we don't see that replicated
as yet and that to us is an opportunity
because one these platforms have a
runway of growth
and within that platform i think the mix
of business that we can do we believe
can be far superior
but these bankers partnership will come
naturally to the
entity or they will have to because i
think they have tie up with the access
bank or
cfc bank which may or may not come to
the most entity we believe they will
come
i mean of course every bank can change
their partners there's nothing that you
know can be
stuck in you know casting stone forever
but we uh believe that they will
continue
uh and so after the deal the icsa banks
state will decline
to below 50 right i think there is a
regulation that a bank can hold
up to 30 percent of them more than 50
percent so
what will happen today it is about
stakeholder transaction
right so what happens to isis bank stake
is that their state goes to roughly
about
uh 48.1 uh and you're right
that there is some regulation that uh
uh typically uh you know rba wants banks
to have
they don't have a corridor between 30
and 50. but there are
uh past presidents uh you know for
example in the case of india infra debt
uh the regulator have
given them some relaxation and i think
what we
are given to understand the bank believe
that they will
be given some dispensation and
sufficient time to bring down to 30
percent if it all
they have to um so so that's the sense
that we have at this point in time
sure and a couple of more questions one
is from
reserving and float do you see
any any issues or any anything that we
have to strengthen going forward
on the on the reserving side so we've
done the diligence and
we've accordingly looked at the
valuation and we honestly as i said you
know we
we like this franchise also because of
the quality of
accounts the governance etc and we think
their
reserving is quite reasonable
and the lastly on the tax uh in fact
there is accumulated losses of around
1600 crores which are sitting for
martial
yeah will those be accrued to us and
whether they will be just
accrued in one year that can be uh
result in a lower tax rate for some
years it should accrue that's part of
you know you know we believe that should
accrue but the point is when it will
approve will depend on when we get the
approvals and all of that
it will depend on the timing and and the
entire benefit will be
taken in one year or it will be we'll
have to look at that gopal you want to
be
you know be more specific on that yeah
so this i think um
obviously uh losses are clearly a
function of what kind of profits you
make
and typically also what happens is
whatever you recognize
uh as book losses may not necessarily be
completely available for tax losses so
that's
based on what the tax statements that
you ascribe and
basis the profits that you make
obviously the losses will get absorbed
over the years so we will have to wait
and see in terms of
uh what kind of profits are we able to
make and then corresponding to the
losses will get absorbed
okay okay so that's it
thank you before we take the next
question we'd like to inform
participants
that in order that the management is
able to address questions from all
participants in the conference
please limit your questions to two per
participant
should you have a follow-up question we
request you to rejoin the queue
the next question is from the lion of
jignesh shell from mk global
please go ahead yeah
thanks very much um
sorry to interrupt but we can't hear you
very clearly if you're in a speaker
request
now yeah this slightly better
yeah is it better now yeah much better
so
i i do had some
i mean most of my questions have been
answered uh specifically on the
valuation but uh you know i
also perceive that seems to be a little
expensive
what has happened uh so
if you can elaborate a little bit
further on on this particular thing
uh but apart from it uh just two quick
questions
one uh the the overall merger impact uh
won't be coming in for 21 right
it will take its only time so probably
assuming that the combined entity
or the combined number should be visible
from alpha 22 is that correct
and number two once the merger merged
number starts coming in
the initial combined ratio should should
be hinting up right i mean gradually
it should be normalizing considering
examining a higher losses out there
so just just these two questions then
yeah so uh
you know it's highly possible that it
will be from 22 it will depend on how
fast we get all approvals so
uh you know it will be on
unlikely with 21 why you will try to do
it you know
push for it as fast as possible uh in
terms of the point that you're making uh
the answer is yes of course
you know as i said you know 120 combined
with 42
expense ratio uh we believe there's a
lot of opportunity to improve the
combined ratio uh
reasonably fast but it won't happen in
one year i mean post closure post you
know the two entities merging
it may take a bit of while uh of time
but thereafter it will definitely
uh begin to show that benefit that is
something that we
believe will happen okay um unless you
understand fine fine that that's it for
myself i'll come back to the q a file a
little more
thanks
thank you the next question is from the
line of age of
frederick from bnk securities please go
ahead
uh thank you for the opportunity sir my
first question is regarding the tech
synergy
so normally what happens is when a
merger happens and
some other distributors find it
difficult to like
find the platform consistent so uh
like what are our thoughts there uh with
respect to the
technology and synergy all that
so uh we've done a reasonable amount of
diligence on the tech stack
uh and we also uh you know
seen what has been happened for the
company on a standalone basis over the
last
couple of years if you look at the total
taking
expenditure that they have is uh you
know surprisingly large
probably because they were using systems
that were
you know of a certain nature and any
case they were
gradually migrating out into new
technology architecture
so our sense is that there should be
going forward
once we do the integration there would
be a fair amount of savings but even in
terms of
the integration migration uh we
are reasonably confident that we will be
able to manage it smoothly
you know i think there are as i said
there's a lot of cultural fit there's a
lot of
leadership you know alignment that is
there uh
you know across the two organizations
where you know i think we'll be able to
manage that well
all right so can you just throw some
more color on
how we are going to bring down the
experiences
if we have thought about it so there are
many
uh elements that we've looked at uh i
don't want to get into the specifics at
this point in them but this suffices to
say that if you look at
you know the obvious fixed costs that
are there let's say the branch
infrastructure cost
some of the elements that i talked about
in the opening remark uh the overall
productivity that you will gain uh as a
merged entity
uh so wherever there are a lot of
overlaps uh
while the overlap is one aspect equally
it gives us an opportunity for
uh synergy benefits so those will
play through as we go along a 42 expense
ratio is
something that we believe we can
definitely bring it down
and the 42 percent excellence ratio is
really not just not because of some
inefficiency by the entity it's just
that
there are some scale challenges at this
size
when unless you reach a certain scale
the expense ratio will always remain
very high for entities and that benefit
we should get when we
integrate the two entities got it
uh thanks thanks for your time
thank you the next question is from
pratik podar from nippon india mutual
fund
please go ahead yeah hi sir sir have you
thought about
relative valuation while describing uh
you know the valuations which you have
to marty
for example if you look at the other
listed companies which are indirectly
listed by
holding companies like show ims general
insurance or magic
both are highly profitable and the chola
ms is today available at 0.5 times to
0.3 times price to float if you were to
think of holding company discounts on
less than i mean zero point six
to zero point nine times price to gwp
solar ms generates 16
roe is highly profitable so have you
thought about
relative valuations or you know
benchmarking while doing this team
that's question number one uh the second
question is uh bankrupt relationships
are there any condition precedence uh
set into the agreement because
uh it would be very difficult to think
about access bank selling ics or combat
products
in a material way and lastly on the
motor side uh the third part if say a
motor dealer bharti plus
lombard becomes for a motor dealer
bharti plus lombard
shares like 80 i'm sure he'll scale it
down to 50 60 he will not keep 100
he would like to have some other uh
player also so have you thought about
these three things
yeah so let me start with the third
first and then go back so as i explained
earlier we
we've looked at oem by oem uh you know
uh presence and the share
of the two entities uh as i said we also
understand on the ground
uh who's doing what in which dealership
so
our sense is that there would be some d
synergies here and there in line with
what you're saying but it won't be
meaningful and any case we baked that
into our uh
and the valuation that we did uh enter
the second question are there cps yes
there are cps
uh in terms of these relationships yeah
on the banking
exactly is there a volume commitment
such that you know more
but you know honestly speaking one thing
that you'll have to look at is
any contract finally while we have a cpa
you know maybe two years later after the
transaction if our bank goes away that's
the failure of our
executive man in all of us right it's
not something with the transaction
we have to then provide value to the
banking partners to be able to
continue with any relationship that's
how we think of
any bank card relation and we've
actually been in the last few years
adding new
private banking relationships and
wherever we've gone in uh
even third we've become the number one
partner in a matter of two to three
years
and that's in spite of us being a in a
sense a competing brand
when it comes to banking so we we
respect the bank banking
relationships the franchise and we are
able to provide value so that we will
have to deliver to all these new
partnerships but to answer your question
there is a ct
into the first look the valuers have
looked at
you know the market benchmarks they've
transactions in the market etc but the
way we look at a
you know value of an entity is based on
dcm which is what we've always talked
about so we've looked at
their business the projections and you
know what we can do once we
uh if and when we uh step in together
and the benefit that we can get out of
combining the two entities so our
uh internal calculation was purely based
on what we believe is a true value
it's not linked to necessarily the
market the market benchmarks is
something that has come out of the
values report what i talked about
but yeah i mean see ultimately whatever
valuations i just quoted are implied by
the market only right so
you could have gone in and said you know
that these are the valuations i'm just
trying to think about
why is there such a big disconnect
between the way you have thought about
multiples versus what the market thinks
about multiples of the listed entities
uh if you i mean i'm sure you guys would
have thought about it right you guys i
would have looked at your
ms saying you know it's trading at such
cheap valuations uh
relative to what we are describing to
bharti aiza and uh chola ms has zero
crop
uh so i'm just trying to think about
that arbitrage where is this arbitrage
or this arbitrage purely because you
believe this is also energy benefits
which we will realize eventually
look you know i can't comment on why the
market is pricing chola at that price
but uh if you look at the actual
transactions that have happened in the
market where
uh you know let's say pe investments
have happened into
entities or similar
strategic investments have happened
let's say in the health side or
in the gi side even minority investment
that have happened
by pe investors using cash has been at
similar multiples
uh so i think that's what the market is
seeing you know
this industry and when we look at it we
obviously look at the cost of capital we
look at the cash flows we look at
what benefits we get in terms of
synergies etc and then we do the dcs
and that's how we arrive at the at the
value that's what we've done we've not
looked at every single
market linked entity as to why someone
is trading at a very low multiple it
could be multiple other factors not
the perceived value of the franchise and
lastly sir uh in your 4 600 of
executable value
how much is synergy uh if you can break
it up into synergy versus
as a standalone basis uh if you've done
this kind of work
or if you can share some bit of is
predominantly a lot of value coming
because you believe in this synergy
no i'm not i mean you know again you
know i can't get more specific than that
but let me tell you that you know of the
total synergy benefit that we believe
we should be able to get we've not
factored the full amount into the
valuation
uh obviously there's a value from the
current franchise in itself
and on top of it there will be some
amount of energy balance right so
how should i think about payback periods
obviously it's a it's a shared share
swap
but if i want to think about payback
periods in terms of
earnings how should i think about that
we've not looked at it that way i mean
if
the way we look at it is you know on a
going concern basis is a merged entity
how are we able to deliver uh you know
growth
in profitability and how do we see our
rvs improve
uh you know post this deal in a couple
of years because initially one or two
years we may have this
uh transitionary uh effect uh when our
sense is that uh this will be are we
accretive to our shareholders in due
course
in the medium term sure so thank you so
much for this all the best
thank you
thank you before we take the next
question a reminder to participants to
please limit your questions to two per
participant
the next question is from my young book
reward from franklin templeton
please go ahead hi
hi thanks for taking my question most of
it is answered
just one thing so bharti access
doing prop business 26 for their
portfolio
i just wanted to check if poster merger
that will continue
or you know based on our approach of not
being in the crop business
would that be discontinued so
our view on crop hasn't materially
changed though this year i think the
crop pricing in the market has improved
for some players
because of lack of capacity as quite a
few of us have vacated
so it's not as if we are suddenly
deciding to write
crop all over again but there are
certain commitments because
most of these contracts now are slightly
long term could be two to three years we
will have to honor those commitments
and as we go along we will make up our
mind whether we want to continue
thereafter or not
uh based on uh how the underlying
business reality of that of the crop
business uh evolves
we've always said that we in our crop we
will look at how the market evolves our
market changes and then we'll come back
if at all
so we'll do the same thing with this
portfolio there are certain commitments
that we have to honor
perfect thank you so much
thank you thank you the next question is
from the line of shantin in chakravati
from edelweiss securities please go
ahead
thank you for the opportunity and
congratulations
on the deal uh my questions are twofold
firstly uh i it will be very helpful if
you could
give some sense of uh you know this
entire cost or standardization that
you're talking about
if you can break it up into some sort of
operating
milestones it's not absolutely
time-based but at least uh you know
purpose based
as to what are the specific areas where
you are going to address
it is going to be general management is
it going to be some distribution
rationalization
is it going to be you know renegotiation
of some of the contracts
each of the milestones of that and how
much they could contribute at a broad
level
and my second question is uh you know
now that you have done this
what would be your incremental both
capacity and appetite for an aggregation
sorry what are the last bits and the
incremental
incremental both capacity and appetite
for further acquisitions i mean within
the next two years can we see anything
more
is it possible after this you know how
much of cheering time does this take
so let me answer the second question and
the specifics and operating cost
i'll ask gopal to share whatever we can
at this stage
uh and i'll cover i'll add anything more
that is required
uh in terms of uh your appetite so you
know one of the things that this will do
is uh even post the uh
combine you know merger of the two
entities uh
we will be quite comfortable on the
solvency side
uh so it is not as if uh we will
get constraint for capital uh after this
but in terms of uh bandwidth uh and
again you know you you've known that
we've kind of talked about
many uh opportunities in the past and uh
we've been very careful about what value
we've paid
and we've let go of certain
opportunities in the past
now we will have to take the same call
in future
we will also have to evaluate the
bandwidth because this will be honestly
a first experience for us in terms of
handling and integration of two entities
and we have to figure out the management
bandwidth
capacity we may have but the bandwidth
factor we will have to study before we
decide inclination we will continue to
remain interested in
deals that make sense uh we what we
believe makes sense for our shareholders
but we will have to understand the
management bandwidth as we go through
this uh
process and by the way before we get
into that this deal has to get
consummated and
you know taken through all uh regulatory
and uh statutory clear
clearances so till that time very
unlikely we'll look at anything
yeah i think i think obviously uh we
would want to look at synergies of all
the points that you meant mentioned
is all a driver of the thought process
that we have
and that is pretty much that we would do
uh in each of those aspects
now when whether you look at let's say
for example on the court side
obviously that will be to look at
breaking down every element of cost
more so in the context of uh the point
that bargo made also with respect to the
branchlet expansions that they have the
objective will be to try and
optimize the presence with respect to
locations so that we are able to have a
relatively larger
footprint through which we are able to
source incremental revenues
similarly equally we will also be
looking at some of the other
administrative expenses that goes into
writing of the business
is something that will again be an area
of focus that we will look at
optimizing and obviously the third
aspect is in order to kind of run the
business
at a scale given that we expect to have
incremental revenues coming in on the
the distribution side that we have
obviously the account will be to again
make sure that we are able to get those
economies of scale coming in with
respect to uh
incremental growth as well so that's the
third aspect that we will focus
and finally of course uh a lot of cost
is also in the context of
the the distribution or let's say the
procurement cost
so that again obviously the attempt will
be to try and work again based on
uh based on growth synergies we will
look at how we are able to optimize
integrates cost structures are concerned
so it will be a combination of all the
four
that will go in so far as costs are
concerned
and this will again be supplemented by
obviously as we are able to get
incremental premiums and to that extent
if you are able to run the business
tightly with higher economies of scale
that by itself should also help us to
realize lower cost ratios so those are
the two things that we would focus on
so it's going to be obviously a
combination of all uh it's not that we
want to put any specific milestones to
say that we will look at only
let's say the costly synergies as a
first milestone and then start looking
at uh let's say distribution cost led
uh synergies that could arise or maybe
the third
aspect of revenues i think all of that
is something that one is going to drive
and in the process as uh we have
outlined over the next few years the
attempt in the medium term will be to
try
and make this activative
okay thank you for your answer
thank you the next question is from the
line of rishi jinjinwala from iifl
please go ahead yeah thanks for the
opportunity
uh i have a couple of questions uh one
just wanted to understand
what are the ways in which we can you
know leverage the bharti enterprises
uh uh you know involvement here you
would mention that at the beginning as
well
and uh you know are there any kind of
lock-ins or any ways in which we
we are you know potentially uh
protecting the current business from
deteriorating
uh till the time merger happens or after
that uh
also in terms of uh you know retaining
uh
the key people in in the company are
there any
uh measures or retention
clauses or anything of that sort that we
have taken care of
so in terms of the first of you know
there is of course
the certain key franchises there in
terms of the
payment bank etc has also the group and
there we have kind of entered to some
amount of contractual
uh you know part of the contract some
certain clauses are already inbuilt we
have a preferential right
in terms of the business there uh in
terms of protecting the business
uh of course there will be the usual uh
you know mechanisms that
we have uh contractually agreed to put
up uh
you know in the interim uh committee
mechanism
through which we will uh ensure that uh
the continuity of existing business is
maintained uh thirdly i think there is
also uh you know i think the team in
bharti actually operating in martial
is uh is we believe a very uh
you know culturally very similar fit
team with a lot of
uh you know innocence past relationship
and uh we have a lot of uh regard for
that team
um so and also we what we've discussed
with the bharti axa
uh with the bharti promoters our theater
promoters is in this period
there are certain uh uh
you know mechanisms that they have
already put in to ensure this happens
so all of that is put in place uh
in terms of going ahead we will
obviously want to
have certain specific uh elements to
which we
then continue the relationship with the
key uh
key talent in those entities that's
something that we will work through as
you go along
but on the shareholding side there is no
lock-in for them okay holding there's no
locking no no
they'll become like a public shareholder
uh
and you know roughly about as you know
7.3 split 51 49 between the two
fair enough and secondly um if i look at
their uh you know motor third party
portfolio so you know from a loss
ratio perspective they were at 109 in fy
97 in fy 20. um
have you done any due diligence in terms
of you know what kind of
provisioning uh that they would have
done just trying to understand whether
how their experience in terms of reserve
triangle has been and could there be any
surprise
risk on the upside or downside there so
these are areas where we
believe we have a fair amount of you
know competence ourselves so we
ourselves done uh you know our own
actual team has looked at it
looked at it with great detail uh
supplemented by uh an actual uh
religions that towers watson has done
and
further uh you know checked because
there's a regular requirement by an
independent actuary
our sense looking at the numbers is that
they are probably one of the better
reserved
uh you know uh businesses today
uh at this point in time and lastly uh
just on you know from our promoter
perspective so
since icsa bank will go down below 50
but how does that work in terms of
consolidation will they continue to have
the control of the board and as a result
consolidation won't get impacted yeah
nothing major changes they'll continue
to have to nominate directors as they
have
isis bank that is uh we will
they will remain the significant large
shareholder
so at least as of now we don't see
anything that is going to change
immediately
okay thank you yeah specific on
consolidation i can't answer that's
something the bank will have to answer
but otherwise from internal operating uh
structures there's not much change and
board control will remain with them
right
they have two nominees today uh or they
had until yesterday they'll continue to
have two nominee directors
uh on our board uh the uh the
marty or axa doesn't have any special
special rights
no thank you
thank you the next question is from the
line of madhukha
from from htfc securities please go
ahead
uh hi uh you know most of my questions
have been answered just uh
you know one question you mentioned that
there were some
uh investment write-offs last year than
fi 20.
uh can you quantify that number yeah
that was
the number right yeah so last year they
kind of provided for about 157 crores
with respect to some of the troubled
investments which is there as a part of
the
list of downgraded investments uh so
that's that's something that they took a
provision
in fi 2020 and what was their
uh overall loss ratio overall loss
issues roughly at about
that's it thank you
thank you the next question is from the
line of deepika mundra from jp morgan
please go ahead uh good evening sir and
thanks for the opportunity
uh so just two questions from my side uh
you've been trying to grow your
retail indemnity health portfolio does
uh
the merger bring anything to the table
regarding that uh like
this is some color on their health book
uh and secondly regarding the bangkok
uh could you clarify as to the duration
or
something around the economics of the
kayak
so on the second one uh deepika
basically what we've contractually
agreed is that
is a continuity of the existing
arrangement without getting into
specifics of
these arrangements on similar commercial
terms uh
so so we stand to benefit in terms of
what they already have
uh in terms of the indemnity and the
health business
uh you know a couple of points one even
their agency channel
uh largely uh you know the products that
dominate the channel is
motor and sme uh and we see an
opportunity of adding
health indemnity to that uh you know
6700 base of
agents not that every agent does help
but we believe there will be
some opportunity there uh similarly on
the banker channel again as i explained
earlier
they seem to have a very much larger
share of motor
in the bank of business relative to what
we've seen for ourselves
now a lot of times when we have in the
past gone into a
you know bank relationship as let's say
the third entity
we've also started with uh you know
maybe sme
or things that the existing part you
know partner wasn't doing
in most cases we've actually been able
to increase our penetration of some of
the preferred products simply because
we've been able to demonstrate
uh you know value to our partner so
we believe there will be similar
opportunities in their uh their
vacation time that they have not just in
terms of
products but also in terms of the
geographical footprint that we have
going into the tier 20
32 cities
got it sir thank you
thank you the next question is from the
line of sanket goda from spark capital
please go ahead uh yeah thanks for the
opportunity
uh just uh because it's two three
questions uh
first first of all what is the
unprovided uh book
of uh on the defaulted bonds of
bhartiyaksa
uh second second question is uh uh um
probably would have won
one one agree in the current year uh so
so what are the states and likely
business compared to eight hundred
eight hundred great outcomes of business
run last year what is the likely
business they will write in the current
year
and and third and third is that uh we
have
135 branches and lombard has their
unfortunate branches
so so so whether there are overlaps
there is a there is an opportunity there
to get synergies
right there and and and and just wanted
to understand how confident
and also on the employees basically
whether you see a significant overlap in
the employees accordingly and
there is a employee cost saving part
into the business
and finally how confident you are to
bring back the
merge density uh the combined ratio back
to 100 percentage that from
current it looks like on performance
basis it looks like around one zero five
percentage right now
yeah so uh you know the on the on the
last two questions let me take and then
i'll uh you know give it back to gopal
to answer those specifics
on the investment etc etc so in terms of
the
last question uh obviously uh
you know we've looked at what we believe
we'll be able to deliver
uh we believe that in our model we've
been conservative
in in how staggered the
improvement will be and i think our
you know in essence internal
attempt will be to beat our own internal
estimates
and that is an execution issue so the
answer is yes now
can i give you a concrete sense on when
we will get to 100
the answer is no but we definitely want
to bring it significantly below the
pro forma merge number as we go along
pretty rapidly
uh in terms of the synergy benefits that
you're talking about into the branch and
some amount of overlaps uh
you know uh in terms of the people
organization
naturally there will be and we will have
to see what
we can we can get out of that but those
are you know
as of now there's a lot of specific
detailing work that would need to be
done but
uh we uh at least the aggregate level
when we looked at
these numbers we see benefits uh
significance energy benefits
uh gopal the other two questions yeah
sorry just to add uh
okay follow up to this point uh so if i
look at bharti
last year they made around 330 crores of
expenditure and advertisement and
branding so so means can we clearly
assume that the 330 cores is the low
lying proof which can be
uh which can be plucked and and the the
operator ratio
of the combined entities can you
significantly improve this
there is still there is a overlap in the
350 code which can't be completely made
zero in that sense because it's a one
entity branding exercise would be one
then
so none of the expensive expenditures we
believe can become exactly zero
uh maybe except for some items but uh i
think the way to look at this
is uh you know as i said in an aggregate
basis they have a 42
expense ratio uh can we shave off
some numbers meaningfully we believe yes
thank you before we take the next
question
i'll just answer the couple of questions
uh i think
on your point on the first question with
respect to is there any amount
resistance required to be provided with
respect to the troubled assets
yes uh so they do have exposures to ilfs
divan
reliance capital and uh yes bank s bank
is hundred percent already provided for
that's
already in fi 2020 with respect to the
other three
uh investments uh as of 31st march 2020
they still had
a book value of about 112 crores which
is something that
we have already kind of considered when
we have looked at
the valuation of the company so that's
112 crores of investments that's still
lying as book value which will get
provided in the normal course
so that's one in so far as crop is
concerned i think
even for 2021 they do have
exposures to crop and as we have said
our objective will be to kind of
honor the commitments uh that balti
access won
in so far as the crop tenders are
concerned and
that's something that we will continue
to honor at this point of time as we
speak
i think the kind of mandates that they
have won on the crop side is pretty much
on the lines as what you have seen for
fi 2020.
thank you before we take the next
question a reminder to participants to
please limit your questions to two per
participant
the next question is from vinod rajamani
from hsbc please go ahead
thank you all my questions are answered
thank you we move to the next question
the next question is from the lion of
nation chavati from kotak please go
ahead
my question thank you
thank you the next question is from the
line of anuj narula
from gm financial please go ahead
yeah so this is money decide january
yep yeah so no so coming back to the
question of accumulated losses and uh so
we just wanted to understand the dta
slash math credit on access book
that lombard can take a benefit of if
you can just throw a little bit light on
it i know
uh you haven't basically done the
numbers
in a finalized form but any rough idea
would help us
yeah so honestly i think why i think
they are all a function of as i said uh
what kind of uh
profits that you make and defer tax i
said by its very nature are items of
timing differences and over a period of
time i think
it will get kind of neutralized based on
the combined
performer numbers in line with what i
had mentioned even with respect to let's
say the
losses that they have so one will have
to look at the aggregate position one
once this entire process of
the approvals are all done and when we
would look at consolidating the position
on that basis we would look at the
ultimate tax positions
in terms of the combined entity and then
give effect to
uh the elements of matters including
any element of a defender to a different
liability situation
thank you thank you
the next question is from the line of
writika dua from illara
please go ahead so thank you my
questions have been answered
thank you the next question is from the
line of
sunrise from reliance general insurance
company limited please go ahead
cycle you may go in with a question
if you can hear us we can't hear you
uh there seems to be no response from
the line of cycle um
we'll move to the next question the next
question is from the line of bhavesh
kanani from ask investment managers
please go ahead thank you for
taking my question uh no
over last many many years we have had a
fairly
good execution tech record and
in context of that just wanted to kind
of
pick your brains on how you approach
this transaction from
a maker by decision as in
what are those factors where we felt
that
we could not make it ourselves and hence
decided to go for a bike
and a subset of this question is
incrementally from here on
what are the areas within a structure
where the buy decision would still be
more effective compared to a make
decision
look that's a good question now if you
look at
make or buy you know is it that we
couldn't have
made any of this maybe some elements it
would have been difficult but lot of it
uh
you know a lot of the part that uh bart
x has today we could have uh
been able to build as well the you know
when we look at a transaction we
look at we look at with a very
pretty uh you know granular lens
in terms of uh how do we create
shareholder value for the amount of
money that we're laying out
and as i said earlier we've in the past
looked at many deals and we've probably
not been able to conjugate them
simply because we've uh we've done we've
followed that practice and that's
something that we've done even here
and when i when we look at the
medium term post you know integration
and the
benefits that we believe we will get out
of this
transaction we believe that this
transaction will be
are we accrued for our shareholders and
the the franchise that we are getting
for the
uh the amount that we are laying out uh
we believe
uh you know we are we are you know we
are actually
not only speeding up our journey but
also
in terms of the aggregate are we benefit
that we are getting
uh we believe it makes sense for for us
at this point in time
and when we do our diligence we probably
are as i said very granular
also because we have our own ground
level understanding of
each business line and how they are
playing out and we
kind of factor all of that into our
hello hello yeah sorry did i answer your
question
yeah one thing more uh just wanted to
get
idea of the areas where you thought it's
better to
go in for a buy right now rather than
build it over a couple of years
just one or two key areas
where the kind of this decision to
go for a buy was making more sense
look our view has been and we've kind of
articulated this for some time that
i think this industry is right for
consolidation and
there is uh you know purely on
consolidation there will be some
significant benefits that will emerge to
players which take this route and
step ahead of the others in terms of
scale
size capability that's number one and
that's the factor that we've always
looked at when we considered this
second we've looked at deals in the past
where we've looked at
uh completely uh uh complementary
areas where you know maybe a certain
franchise could have added a new element
to us that's another way of looking at
it and we are always open to those
transactions also
but this one was more in terms of the
first aspect that i talked about
on top of it there were certain uh very
powerful distribution
platforms that they have which we
believe could be of great value
to the combined entity in in the future
both in terms of uh
specific dealer relationship and share
of certain
oem partners as also in the bank
assurance side
the agency number of course the 6700
agents to add that
is also you know a fair amount of effort
uh and that
comes in on top of both these two
okay okay thanks for answering my
question that's all
thank you the next question is from
sandeep jain from bidlas and life
insurance please go ahead
yeah uh most of the thing has been
answered just uh
one thing on the hill side is bharti
working on the same style that you are
working like uh it's not a tpa kind of
you're working directly with hospitals
bharati is working or is there any
synergy out there also gopal you want to
take that
because i think that motor is la motor
is more of in-house
health is really a capability that we
are building uh as we speak
so at this point of time that's the area
where we would definitely see as an
opportunity at the level of scale at
which their business is
they are they are not necessarily uh
announced
the health claim servicing function but
uh
in terms of the opportunity for growth
or runway for growth that's a segment
that we will clearly look at
ramping up and we will you continue to
leverage
the capability that isis number has
created in terms of in sourcing
or enhancing those claim settlement
practices
okay so they they are not in they are
not in uh
in in-house uh um game settlement they
are doing with tpa right
that's right and you will bring it back
to lombard's platform
yeah we will obviously evaluate every
contract appropriately but the direction
will be that
okay thank you
thank you
we'll be able to take one last question
we take the last question from the line
of ashish sharma from innom asset
management please go ahead
yeah uh thanks for the opportunity sir
uh just one uh
clarification on on the on the stake uh
of
icc bank forced the transaction so uh
so i mean bank the parent had sold some
stake and now the steak is below 50
uh so we shouldn't presume that uh the
parents
would want to keep it uh closer to 50
percent uh
when to maintain the majority stake and
also
of a financial investment for them and
will there be any lock-in
for uh for uh supposed to be
so in terms of the bank as i explained
that you know there are certain
regulations which
indicate that for a bank if you go below
50 they're supposed to bring it under
30 but there are precedence in the past
where
banks have been allowed to hold between
this range
and our sense from what we understand
from the bank
is that you know they would obviously be
making applications so that they can
hold
uh you know on to this share and if at
all they have to bring it under
230 they will take uh they will get time
to do it
you know you know you know in terms of
doing it
in a disciplined manner uh in terms of
but otherwise i think from a bank's
perspective
clearly they want to remain uh the
number one shareholder the
promoter of this entity and we will
remain
uh one of the large you know entities of
the banking of isis group
but that doesn't change uh now coming to
your second question on axa
yes you know they are really becoming a
public shareholder
you know a minority uh about roughly uh
3.7
3.5 but
the at least our discussion with them is
uh the fact that they are continuing to
remain very keen
on certain areas of the indian market
and we've already had some discussions
on
how we can partner and do uh certain uh
you know bring some of the solutions
that they have
to the indian market you know one of the
advantages that we
possibly have you know relative to you
know
a mid-sized entity is scale particularly
into the smaller markets
and some of the tie-ups with large
distribution formats that we
we also have and they see value in this
partnership
even in terms of some of these strategic
agendas that they have so
clearly you know our conversation with
them has been that we will want to work
together to see
how we can uh mutually benefit from this
association perfect
thank you and all the best thank you
thank you
thank you very much we'll take that as
the last question
i would now like to hand the conference
back to mr bhagava scripture for closing
comments
uh thank you thank you everyone uh you
know i guess a great set of questions uh
for us
this is uh as i said an important uh
decision uh
we've been open to inaudib kind of
been you know looking at you know
opportunities but we've been very
careful about what we
do and what we buy and in that context
we are quite excited about this
opportunity in terms of creating
shareholder fire value in the medium
term
for all of us so again thank you for
joining us today
and feel free to reach out separately if
you have
more questions thank you
thank you very much